We're talking about when is it time to end friendships.
Let me just say something.
I know that I come off as like very self-righteous to some people.
It's not even that I think I'm better or that I think I'm more righteous.
I just be like really trying to do the right thing.
And I feel like so many folks like really are like, yeah, like it's just.
Everybody doesn't have that set of morals.
And I think that's when it's time to end a friendship or relationship when your morals
and integrity don't match up, especially depending on like if your friend or someone
you thought was your friend is a Trump supporter and you're not.
And now you saying things supporting him and you pissing me off if I don't support him,
you know, so now I don't want to talk to you, but I might love you as my friend.
But our differences, either we just can't have this conversation or we can't.
We can't be friends.
Yeah.
Tough times with friendships and relationships regarding politics.
I don't think it's ever been like this since I've been alive.
That has been such a whole of polarizing figures in politics.
But I do wonder back in the 60s during the civil rights movement, how many friendships
ended with people who were like, why y'all stirring up trouble?
Well, we can't be friends no more.
You know, if you if you're not going to be a safe harbor as we try and change this world
for a better place, what are we doing?
And that's for me as basic as it gets.